aimoo.com 2001-06-14

# Free message board free poll free chatroom online community

**Aimoo Community Privacy Policy**

 **Overall Privacy Statement**  
Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of the Aimoo Community Network, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.

 **1\. Information Aimoo Community Gathers and Tracks**  
Aimoo Community gathers two types of information about users: data that users provide through optional, voluntary registration; and data Aimoo Community gathers through tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views and message posts throughout the Aimoo Community Network. Such information enables us to better tailor our features and content to users' needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. Because the Aimoo Community Express Service derives its revenue mainly from advertising, providing aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users.

Aimoo Community currently gathers user information in the following processes:

 _Optional Registration_  
Aimoo Community offers free, voluntary registration to users. By registering, users can enter message boards without having to log in each time; they can post new messages and reply to existing messages; they can take advantage of personalization (the ability to filter messages according to a user-supplied criteria); and they have the ability to create new message boards.

During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, and email address, and must answer mandatory survey questions about age, gender, zip code, and country.

In addition, when a registered user creates a new message board, Aimoo Community requires information on the Web site the board will be used on, including: site name, site URL, estimated site traffic, and site type. Aimoo Community also asks for an optional description of the site.

 _Optional User Profile Information_  
Registered Aimoo Community users have the option of displaying additional personal information about themselves through the User Profile form. All fields contained in the User Profile form are optional. These fields may include, but are not limited to, the following: URL link to photo, home page URL, city, occupation, birth date, marital status, ICQ number, hobbies/interests, personal quote, user's last 10 posts, and user's bookmarks. The user can choose to display or not display any or all information using the My Account management area. None of the information contained within the User Profile form will be transmitted to any third party without the user's express consent.

 _Surveys_  
Occasionally, Aimoo Community conducts user surveys to better understand the needs of our audience in order to improve our features. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party without user's express consent.

 _Usage Tracking_  
Aimoo Community tracks user traffic patterns (e.g., which message boards you visit) throughout aimoo.com and the Aimoo Community Network. This information may be used to help personalize the Aimoo Community service or target advertising. Aimoo Community also breaks down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).

 _Cookies_  
A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Aimoo Community uses cookies to allow automatic logins and to track user traffic patterns (as described above).

When you register, Aimoo Community uses a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on our site. Cookies also enable you to enter Aimoo Community Network message boards as a member without having to log on each time.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to read messages on the Aimoo Community Network. However, you do need cookies to post messages and to create and manage message boards.

 **2\. Use of the Information**  
Aimoo Community uses any information given by our users to enhance their experience, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the Aimoo Community Network or to better prepare future features based on the interests of our users.

Aimoo Community uses your email information to provide more personalized message board features. At a user's request we will send out emails notifying the user of replies to specific message board postings. We also provide the option for the user to allow other users to respond to postings directly via their email. Finally, for users who create message boards, we provide many board management tools that the user can opt to receive via email. Aimoo Community may also send the user email notifications of specific changes to our service. Aimoo Community never shares individual email addresses with any third parties, including advertisers or partners, without prior consent from our users.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of the Aimoo Community Network users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. Aimoo Community does not track what messages individual users read, but rather how well each message board and feature performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

Aimoo Community creates aggregrate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs.

 **3\. Sharing of the Information**  
Aimoo Community uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and to help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our Express Service free. We do not share individually identifiable information about specific users with any third party without prior consent from the user. Aimoo Community does not control the practices of our advertisers. If you have questions about how one of our advertisers uses information about you when you click their ad and go to their content, please contact them directly (Aimoo Community will divulge information only as necessary to comply with state and federal laws.)

 **4\. Opt-out Policy**  
Aimoo Community gives users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

  * Opting not to receive our electronic messages
  * Opting not to provide certain optional personal information when registering for an account (see above)
  * Opting not to participate in message posting or board creation, which completely alleviates the need to register for an account or to provide identifiable information

 **5\. Correct/Update Policy**  
Aimoo Community offers users the ability to correct or change the information collected during registration process (see above). The instructions for doing this can be found by clicking on the "My Profile" link. Users may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. Users may also delete their account at any time by contacting [support@aimoo.com](mailto:support@aimoo.com) (all profile information, excluding old message postings, will be eliminated from our records). Users who are experiencing problems or who have any questions about how our services work can contact us at [support@aimoo.com](mailto:support@aimoo.com).
